Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
Vernon Historical Society
Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
1952 to 1979
Manchester Evening Herald
12 linear feet 6 boxes
Vernon Historical Society
The collection contains photo negatives, photographs and news clippings from articles published in The Manchester Evening Herald. The images relate to articles featuring local people, businesses, or social, cultural or political events that occurred between 1952 and 1979.
Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
In 1991 the Manchester Historical Society gave the Vernon Historical Society a collection of photo negatives, photograph and news clipping from defunct Manchester Evening Herald newspaper of Manchester, Connecticut
Biography
When The Manchester Evening Herald newspaper from Manchester Connecticut ceased publication in 1981, they turned over their archives to the Manchester Historical Society. In 1991 the Society removed negatives, clippings and photographs from the archive that related to towns outside of Manchester and offered the materials to local historical societies or libraries.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection consists of images taken to accompany articles in the paper. The bulk of the collection consists of photo negatives. Some photographs were submitted by people or businesses or political campaigns for an article. This collection of images aligns with articles of local interest. Topics include elections, political campaigns, business stories, school events, social events, community activities. The collection provides insight into local happenings for the 1950s through the 1970s.
Arrangement
The images are arranged chronologocialy. Each set of images is in an acid free photo envelope with the original paper sleeve included. For each set of images, we asked a photograph to print one negative as a photo to help with preparing a subject catalog. The collection fills 6 boxes. A subject catalog with location information for each image has been entered into an Excel spread sheet.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Manchester Evening Herald, Manchester, Connecticut; Vernon, Connecticut; Rockville, Connecticut; Photographs; Black and White Negatives; Newspaper Clippings
Separated Material
A separate box has related news clippings from the original articles.
- Inventory
  - Captains - Baseball Team, 4/7/1952; Names: Gerald Kuhnly, Glenn Narkon| Topics: RHS; Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.1)
  - Baseball Team, 4/7/1952; Topics: RHS; Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.2)
  - Rockville Little League with awards, 11/1/1952; Topics: Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.3)
  - Shirley M. Holmes engaged, 2/2/1955; Names: Shirley Holmes| Topics: Marriage & Family; Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.4)
  - Edmund F. Dwyer - new Deputy Sheriff, 9/22/1955; Names: Edmund Dwyer| Topics: Police Dept.; Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.5)
  - Edmund F. Dwyer, 11/1/1955; Names: Edmund Dwyer| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.6)
  - Harry Hammer, attorney, 12/15/1955; Names: Harry Hammer | Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 1, Folder MH.7)
  - Mrs. Raymond Spielman-Emblem Club, 5/2/1956; Names: Mrs. Raymond Spielman| Topics: Clipping; Social Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.8)
  - Thomas J. Larkin-obituary, 6/9/1957; Names: Thomas J. Larkin (Box 1, Folder MH.9)
  - Seymour Lavitt, 9/19/1957; Names: Seymour Lavitt (Box 1, Folder MH.10)
  - Lu Scarlato owner Manchester Beauty Salon, 9/25/1957; Names: Lu Scarlato| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.11)
  - John Scarlato owner Manchester Beauty Salon, 9/25/1957; Names: John Scarlato (Box 1, Folder MH.12)
  - Barbara Cox, 12/27/1957; Names: Barbara Cox| Topics: Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.13)
  - Antoni Sadlak, 5/11/1905; Names: Antoni Sadlak| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.14)
  - Seymour Lavitt, Man of the Year Rotary Club, 6/23/1958; Names: Seymour Lavitt| Topics: Clipping; Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.15)
  - Harry Hammer, Running for office, 11/3/1958; Names: Harry Hammer | Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping; Law and Lawyers (Box 1, Folder MH.16)
  - Harvey A. Yonce, 2/12/1959; Names: Harvey A. Yonce| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 1, Folder MH.17)
  - George Trapp, 3/3/1960; Names: George Trapp| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.18)
  - Mr & Mrs R Genovese - 40th anniversary, 12/6/1960; Names: R. Genovese| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 1, Folder MH.19)
  - John F. Sommers, 3/22/1961; Names: John F. Sommers (Box 1, Folder MH.20)
  - Former firehouse behind Vernon Ctr church, 5/1/1961; Topics: Fire Dept.; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.21)
  - Model-Barnes Boats, 5/1/1961; Topics: Businesses (Box 1, Folder MH.22)
  - Hawaiian Nite in Talcottville, 5/3/1961; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.23)
  - Mayor Flaherty buys 1st poppy, 5/3/1961; Names: Leo Flaherty| Topics: Veterans (Box 1, Folder MH.24)
  - Ecker Farm, 5/1/1961; Topics: Vernon Center; Farming (Box 1, Folder MH.25)
  - Sgt. Barlett hearing, 5/18/1961; Names: Sgt. Barlett| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.26)
  - Ground breaking-St. John's- Vernon, 5/22/1961; Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.27)
  - Flag raising-Rockville, 5/31/1961; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.28)
  - Straw Hat Fair-Vernon, 5/31/1961; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.29)
  - End of Barlett hearing, 6/3/1961; Names: Sgt. Barlett| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.30)
  - Strawberry Festival-Vernon R.C. Church, 6/12/1961; Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.31)
  - O'Connor, 6/21/1961; Names: O'Connor| Topics: Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.32)
  - New Highway Signs-Vernon Circle, 6/21/1961; Topics: Transportation (Box 1, Folder MH.33)
  - RHS Graduation-Rockville, 6/23/1961; Topics: RHS (Box 1, Folder MH.34)
  - Vernon Consolidation Vote, 6/27/1961; Topics: Consolidation (Box 1, Folder MH.35)
  - Budget Hearing-Vernon Fire District, 7/12/1961; Topics: Town Government (Box 1, Folder MH.36)
  - New Red Cross Director-Rockville, 7/20/1961; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.37)
  - Sgt. Barlett Case-Rockville, 7/28/1961; Names: Sgt. Barlett| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.38)
  - Draft Board on Vacation-Rockville, 8/1/1961; Topics: Military Service (Box 1, Folder MH.39)
  - Franklin Park contest winner-Rockville, 8/1/1961; Topics: Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.40)
  - Boothroyd returns to Rockville, 8/2/1961; 0 (Box 1, Folder MH.41)
  - Rededication of Tower-Rockville, 8/11/1961; Topics: Landmarks (Box 1, Folder MH.42)
  - George Trapp & his chickens-Rockville, 8/31/1961; Names: George Trapp| Topics: Farming (Box 1, Folder MH.43)
  - George Trapp, his children, & chickens, 8/31/1961; Names: George Trapp| Topics: Farming (Box 1, Folder MH.44)
  - Building "B"-Rockville, 9/6/1961; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 1, Folder MH.45)
  - Vernon "Manhunt", 9/8/1961; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.46)
  - GOP Dinner-Vernon, 11/11/1961; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.47)
  - Rev. Nubert (?) Honored, 11/11/1961; Names: Rev. Nubert| Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.48)
  - Accident-Wilbur Cross Highway-Ver/Tol, 11/11/1961; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.49)
  - Meet the Candidates-Dem. Headquarters, 9/28/1961; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.50)
  - Ed May with GOP-Rockville, 10/??/61; Names: Ed May| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.51)
  - Rockville and Vernon Elections, 10/3/1961; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.52)
  - Pumpkin Festival-Talcottville, 10/5/1961; Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.53)
  - Maple Street School Addition, 10/12/1961; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 1, Folder MH.54)
  - Mr. & Mrs. E. Dauphise 60th Anniversary-Rock, 10/20/1961; Names: Dauphise, E| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 1, Folder MH.55)
  - Gov. Dempsey & Mayor Flaherty-Rockville, 11/??/61; Names: DempseyFlaherty| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.56)
  - St. John's Church-Vernon, 11/2/1961; Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.57)
  - Performers at Benefit for Cindy Sandberg-Vernon, 11/3/1961; Topics: Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.58)
  - Home Eco. Dept. Play-RH School, 11/3/1961; Topics: RHS (Box 1, Folder MH.59)
  - Fashion Show-Talcottville Cong. Church, 11/11/1961; Topics: Churches; Entertainment; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.60)
  - B I E Day-Vernon/Rockville, 11/13/1961; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 1, Folder MH.61)
  - Fire-Rockville, 11/28/1961; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.62)
  - Mrs. Ruth Ventura, 4/12/1962; Names: Ruth Ventura (Box 1, Folder MH.63)
  - Muriel Lambert,Officer-Rainbow Girls, 5/15/1962; Names: Muriel Lambert| Topics: Clipping; Social Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.64)
  - Paul J. Bowman-Rockville, 9/1/1962; Names: Paul J. Bowman| Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.65)
  - Two boys with rocket-Vernon, 10/16/1962; Topics: Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.66)
  - Methodist Church Mortgage Burning-Vernon, 11/5/1961; Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.67)
  - Japanese Room-Talcottville, 11/12/1962; Topics: Social Organizations; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.68)
  - Fire at Merton's-Rockville, 12/5/1962; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.69)
  - Fire-Vernon, 12/30/1962; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.70)
  - Redevelopment Agency-R Railroad Station, 1/10/1963; Topics: Transportation; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 1, Folder MH.71)
  - Fire-Vernon, 6/7/1963; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.72)
  - Flag Day-Rockville, 6/14/1963; Topics: Holidays (Box 1, Folder MH.73)
  - Ground breaking-Elderly Project-Rockville, 6/19/1963; Topics: Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 1, Folder MH.74)
  - Strawberry Festival-Sacred Heart Church-Ver., 6/19/1963; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.75)
  - RGH Graduation-Vernon, 6/20/1963; Topics: RHS (Box 1, Folder MH.76)
  - Art Show-Rockville Hospital, 6/24/1963; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Arts (Box 1, Folder MH.77)
  - Five Day Old Colt Vernon Gleason Ranch, 7/6/1963; Names: John Gleason| Topics: Farming (Box 1, Folder MH.78)
  - Fire Drill St. Bernard's School-Rockville, 10/11/1963; Topics: Schools & Education; Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.79)
  - Broken Water Main Filterbed Rd-Rockville, 7/16/1963; Topics: Town Government (Box 1, Folder MH.80)
  - Fire-Rockville, Brooklyn Street, 7/20/1963; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.81)
  - Fire-Rockville-Elk's Club Carriage House, 7/23/1963; Topics: Fire Dept.; Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.82)
  - Fire-Rockville-Market Street, 7/27/1963; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.83)
  - Fire-Vernon Sunrise Drive, 7/27/1963; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.84)
  - Business building Vernon-Rt 83 Bowling Alley, 7/27/1963; Topics: Businesses; Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.85)
  - George Trapp-Police Chief-Rockville, 8/14/1963; Names: George Trapp| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.86)
  - Accident-Vernon Rt 83, 7/30/1963; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation (Box 1, Folder MH.87)
  - Fire-Rockville-Davis Ave, 8/9/1963; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.88)
  - 2 New police Officers-Rockville, 8/30/1963; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.89)
  - Fire-Labor Day-Rockville, 9/3/1963; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.90)
  - Case Building-Rockville, 9/6/1963; Topics: Businesses; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 1, Folder MH.91)
  - AAA Safety Awards-Rockville, 9/6/1963; Names: Leo Flaherty| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.92)
  - Barrows & Wallace Houses in Vernon, 9/12/1963; Topics: Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.93)
  - Ground Breaking CO.3 Fire House-Talcottville, 9/23/1963; Topics: Fire Dept.; Transportation (Box 1, Folder MH.94)
  - Landscapes-Talcottville Pond, 9/24/1963; Topics: Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.95)
  - Heralding Homes-Tumblebrook Road-Vernon, 9/28/1963; Names: Polly Beckley| Topics: Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.96)
  - Valerie Ford engagement to John DeQuattro, 10/??/63; Names: Valerie Ford| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 1, Folder MH.97)
  - Robert Garabedian, Pres. Of Chamber of Commerce, 10/??/63; Names: Robert Garabedian| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.98)
  - Elections-Rockville, 10/8/1963; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.99)
  - Selectmen and Voting Court-Vernon, 10/8/1963; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.100)
  - Elderly Housing-Framework-Rockville, 10/24/1963; Topics: Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 1, Folder MH.101)
  - Elderly Housing-Rockville, 10/24/1963; Topics: Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 1, Folder MH.102)
  - Fire-Woods-Rockville, 10/24/1963; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.103)
  - Window Painting-Rockville, 10/30/1963; Topics: Businesses; Holidays (Box 1, Folder MH.104)
  - John DeQuattro & Valerie Ford Wedding, 6/22/1964; Names: DeQuattro/Ford| Topics: Marriage & Family; Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.105)
  - Christmas Parade-Rockville, 11/30/1964; Topics: Holidays (Box 1, Folder MH.106)
  - John Canaveri, Coach, RHS, 12/??/64; Names: John Canaveri| Topics: RHS (Box 1, Folder MH.107)
  - Eagle Scouts- Rockville, 12/4/1964; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.108)
  - Fireman's Toys for Tots Christmas, 12/23/1964; Topics: Fire Dept.; Holidays (Box 1, Folder MH.109)
  - Ambulance Vehicle-Vernon, 5/18/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Rockville Hospital (Box 1, Folder MH.110)
  - Man with Mask next to ambulance-Vernon, ??/??/65; Topics: Fire Dept.; Rockville Hospital (Box 1, Folder MH.111)
  - Fitzgerald Ford-Rockville, ??/??/65; Topics: Businesses; Transportation (Box 1, Folder MH.112)
  - Tree Down-Vernon-Bolton Road, 1/2/1965; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.113)
  - Skiing, Fox Hill, Rockville, 1/4/1965; Topics: Recreation (Box 1, Folder MH.114)
  - Chicken coop burned by Vernon Firemen, 1/12/1965; Names: Oakhurst Farm| Topics: Fire Dept.; Businesses; Farming (Box 1, Folder MH.115)
  - Accident-Vernon, 1/18/1965; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation (Box 1, Folder MH.116)
  - Fire-Rockville, 1/18/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.117)
  - Award-Firemen-Rockville, 1/19/1965; Names: Leo Flaherty| Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.118)
  - Salvaging bell fromVernon Cong Church, 1/27/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Churches; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.119)
  - Vernon Congreg. receives money to rebuild, 1/28/1965; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.120)
  - Jr. High School contract signed-Vernon, 1/29/1965; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 1, Folder MH.121)
  - Rev. Paul Bowman, 1/29/1965; Names: Paul Bowman| Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.122)
  - Samuel Pearl, candidate for Mayor, Vernon, 02/??/65; Names: Samuel Pearl| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 1, Folder MH.123)
  - Raymond E Spielman-Obituary-Vernon, 02/??/65; Names: Raymond E Spielman (Box 1, Folder MH.124)
  - Thomas Wolff, 02/??/65; Names: Thomas Wolff (Box 1, Folder MH.125)
  - David Hayes-Eagle Scout Award-Talcottville, 02/??/65; Names: David Hayes| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.126)
  - Freight Station Demonstration-Rockville, 02/??/65; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 1, Folder MH.127)
  - Six days before fire-Vernon Cong Church, 2/2/1965; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.128)
  - Acorn Planting-Talcottville School, 2/2/1965; Topics: Schools & Education; Talcottville (Box 1, Folder MH.129)
  - Fire-Rockville-Talcott Avenue, 2/2/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.130)
  - $1,000 check to church, Vernon Cong, 2/9/1965; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.131)
  - Rotary presents tables & chairs - Franklin Park, 2/18/1965; Topics: Civic Organizations; Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 1, Folder MH.132)
  - Jr. Women's Club Fashion Show-Vernon, 2/26/1965; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.133)
  - Castles display at Rockville Library, 03/??/65; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 1, Folder MH.134)
  - Foreign students visit filtration plant-Rockville, 3/1/1965; Topics: Town Government; Public Health (Box 1, Folder MH.135)
  - Town elections-Vernon, 3/3/1965; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 1, Folder MH.136)
  - Baton twirlers-Rockville, 3/19/1965; Topics: Entertainment (Box 1, Folder MH.137)
  - Federal Housing dedication-Rockville, 3/25/1965; Topics: Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 1, Folder MH.138)
  - Rockville Library addition rendering, 04/??/65; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 1, Folder MH.139)
  - Musical rehearsal for 1st Cong Church Fund, 04/??/65; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 1, Folder MH.140)
  - Apartment fire-Vernon Gardens-Vernon, 04/??/65; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 1, Folder MH.141)
  - Fire-Fox Hill-Rockville, 4/5/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Parks (Box 1, Folder MH.142)
  - Science Fair Winners-Rockville High School, 4/9/1965; Topics: RHS (Box 1, Folder MH.143)
  - Alden Spinning Mill Banquet-Talcottville, 4/10/1965; Topics: Talcottville; Mills and Factories (Box 1, Folder MH.144)
  - Easter Sunrise Service-Fox Hill-Rockville, 4/9/1965; Topics: Churches; Parks; Holidays (Box 1, Folder MH.145)
  - Easter Services-St. Bernard's-Rockville, 4/19/1965; Topics: Churches (Box 1, Folder MH.146)
  - Boy Scout Flags to Troop #83 Vernon from E&L, 5/7/1965; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 1, Folder MH.147)
  - Men charged with Market St murders-Rockville, 5/10/1965; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder MH.148)
  - Market St Murder-Police look for evidence-Rockville, 5/10/1965; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.149)
  - Dr.Neil Mara opens medical practice-Vernon, 5/11/1965; Names: Neil Mara| Topics: Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.150)
  - Vernon Firemen's Scholarship Check-RGH, 5/18/1965; Topics: RHS; Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.151)
  - Covering Hockanum River-Rockville, 5/13/1965; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.152)
  - Town & Country Players-Rehearsal-Rockville, 5/17/1965; Topics: Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.153)
  - Demolishing the Rady Building-Rockville, 5/21/1965; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.154)
  - Television Filming-RGH-Rockville, 5/25/1965; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.155)
  - Hintz House with pink decorations-Vernon, 5/27/1965; Topics: Housing (Box 2, Folder MH.156)
  - Accident-Hockanum River-Rockville, 6/1/1965; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation (Box 2, Folder MH.157)
  - Fire-Rockville, 6/14/1965; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.158)
  - Graduation-Rockville High School, 6/24/1965; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.159)
  - Fire-Rockville, 6/24/1965; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.160)
  - Mrs. Phillip Atkins,160 Taylor St,YNK-Talcottville, 6/30/1965; Names: Mrs. Atkins| Topics: Talcottville (Box 2, Folder MH.161)
  - RGH "Hi Fever Follies"-Rockville, 7/27/1965; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.162)
  - Fire at Grove Hill Cemetery-Rockville, 7/29/1965; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.163)
  - Mayor McClusker hands out ice cream, 7/29/1965; Names: Mayor McClusker| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.164)
  - Weeping Willow downed by storm-Rockville, 8/11/1965; Topics: Environment (Box 2, Folder MH.165)
  - Rockville Pub. Library summer readers & cake, 8/18/1965; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 2, Folder MH.166)
  - Rockville Hotel Demolished-Rockville, 8/25/1965; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.167)
  - Accident-Rockville, 9/2/1965; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.168)
  - Mrs.Stanley Pearson,83 Merline,Ver,recipe for YNK, 9/2/1965; Names: Mrs. Pearson (Box 2, Folder MH.169)
  - Ernie Scranton-Scranton Motors-Rockville, 9/9/1965; Names: Ernie Scranton| Topics: Businesses (Box 2, Folder MH.170)
  - Fire-Rockville, 9/14/1965; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.171)
  - Fire-Fox Hill Apartments-Rockville, 9/14/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 2, Folder MH.172)
  - Charles O. Talcott, 9/26/1965; Names: Charles O. Talcott (Box 2, Folder MH.173)
  - Fire Drill at St. Joseph's-Rockville, 10/7/1965; Topics: Schools & Education; Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.174)
  - Jr. Fire Marshalls at St. Joseph's-Rockville, 10/7/1965; Topics: Schools & Education; Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.175)
  - Fire Drill at Vernon Circle-Vernon, 10/11/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.176)
  - Vernon Women's Club Rodeo-Vernon, 10/5/1965; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.177)
  - Mary Mary rehearsal-Rockville, 11/5/1965; Topics: Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.178)
  - First Cong. Church Groundbreaking-Vernon, 11/8/1965; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 2, Folder MH.179)
  - Accident-Rockville, 11/10/1965; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.180)
  - East Coast Blackout, Kids working by candlelight, 11/10/1965; Topics: National Events (Box 2, Folder MH.181)
  - Inside the Sports Center-Rockville, 11/10/1965; Topics: Businesses (Box 2, Folder MH.182)
  - Sacred Heart Fair-Vernon, 11/11/1965; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.183)
  - Winning Book Posters-Lake St School-Vernon, 11/11/1965; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 2, Folder MH.184)
  - Christmas Parade-Rockville, 11/29/1965; Topics: Fire Dept.; Holidays (Box 2, Folder MH.185)
  - Christmas Parade-Gene Pitney, Parade Marshall, 11/29/1965; Names: Gene Pitney| Topics: Holidays (Box 2, Folder MH.186)
  - Rev. R. E. Bertram-new pastor,1st Evang.Luth.Church, 8/19/1966; Names: Richard Bertram| Topics: Clipping; Churches (Box 2, Folder MH.187)
  - Dinner for John Dempsey-Rockville, 10/14/1966; Names: John Dempsey| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.188)
  - Vernon Riding Stables-Hayride-Vernon, 12/30/1966; Topics: Businesses; Entertainment; Farming (Box 2, Folder MH.189)
  - Edward Mar takes post in Building Dept-Rockville, 1/23/1967; Names: Edward Mar| Topics: Clipping; Town Government (Box 2, Folder MH.190)
  - Percy Spicer-Vernon, 03/??/67; Names: Percy Spicer (Box 2, Folder MH.191)
  - Pete Martello in baseball uniform, 3/10/1967; Names: Pete Martello| Topics: Recreation; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.192)
  - Linda L. Bruce engaged-Rockville, 3/20/1967; Names: Linda L. Bruce| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.193)
  - Atty Frank McCoy-Vernon, 4/5/1967; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Clipping; Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.194)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy-Vernon, 4/5/1967; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.195)
  - Anne Hepton engaged-Rockville, 4/11/1967; Names: Anne Hepton| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.196)
  - Harry S. Godi,Dean of Adm at MCC-Vernon, 7/28/1967; Names: Harry S. Godi| Topics: Schools & Education; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.197)
  - Kenneth Nelson,Nelson freightways,on panel,Ver, 8/1/1967; Names: Kenneth Nelson| Topics: Businesses (Box 2, Folder MH.198)
  - Joe Saternis won 1st prize in NE photo contest,Ver, 9/30/1967; Names: Joe Saternis (Box 2, Folder MH.199)
  - Prize winning photo taken by Joe Saternis-Ver, 9/30/1967; Names: Joe Saternis| Topics: Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.200)
  - Tri City Plaza-Vernon, 11/10/1967; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.201)
  - Tri City Plaza-Vernon, 11/10/1967; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.202)
  - Joseph Lucas-accused of sister's murder-Vernon, 1/17/1968; Names: Joseph Lucas| Topics: Police Dept.; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.203)
  - Rockville Jaycee Man of Year-Rockville, 1/23/1968; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 2, Folder MH.204)
  - Wedding pic. of Linda Bruce,married Stanley Hilinski, 4/29/1968; Names: Linda Bruce| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.205)
  - Paul Sweeney, Tolland County Sheriff-Vernon, 6/14/1968; Names: Paul Sweeney| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.206)